<CATALOG>
	 <CD>
			 <title>A Vida Que Eu Escolhi</title>
			 <artist>Tony Carreira</artist>
			 <artwork>https://img.discogs.com/ZrC2cjDjuh_mremQ6o5kXKlTFAQ=/fit-in/300x300/filters:strip_icc():format(jpeg):mode_rgb():quality(40)/discogs-images/R-5263584-1389034439-9728.jpeg.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>PT</country>
			 <company>Espacial</company>
			 <description>A Vida Que Eu Escolhi é o décimo segundo álbum de estúdio a solo do cantor português Tony Carreira. Foi lançado em 2006 pela editora Espacial. Contém 15 faixas, das quais se destacam "Mesmo Que Seja Mentira" e "É Melhor (Dizer Adeus)" (anteriormente editadas como extras no álbum Ao Vivo no Coliseu, também de 2006), bem como "O Que Vai Ser De Mim (Quando Fores Embora)" e "A Vida Que Eu Escolhi", 4 temas que fazem parte da compilação "20 Anos de Canções", lançada em 2008.
Este trabalho esteve, ao todo, 64 semanas, no Top Oficial da AFP, a tabela semanal dos 30 álbuns mais vendidos em Portugal. Entrou na época de Natal de 2006 directamente para a 4ª posição, atingindo o 1º lugar à quarta semana, lugar que disputaria com André Sardet e Madonna e que ocuparia por mais 3 ocasiões mas que perderia definitivamente para José Afonso. </description>
			 <year>2006</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Hide Your Heart</title>
			 <artist>Bonnie Tyler</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/2/23/Hide_Your_Heart_Front_Cover.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>CBS Records</company>
			 <description>Hide Your Heart (released under the title Notes from America in the United States, Canada and Brazil), is the seventh studio album by Welsh singer Bonnie Tyler. The album features the song "Hide Your Heart" written by Paul Stanley, Desmond Child and Holly Knight. This song was later covered three times in 1989 Ace Frehley's Trouble Walkin', Robin Beck's Trouble Or Nothin', and Molly Hatchet's Lightning Strikes Twice. And performed in 1989 by Paul Stanley with Kiss on their Hot in the Shade album. </description>
			 <year>1988</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Greatest Hits</title>
			 <artist>Dolly Parton</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/3c/Dollygreatesthits.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>RCA</company>
			 <description>Greatest Hits is a compilation album by Dolly Parton, released in October 1982. It focused mostly on Parton's late 1970s pop hits. The original track list was revised a year later to include Parton's 1983 duet hit with Kenny Rogers, "Islands in the Stream". The album has since been reissued with an abbreviated track listing. The 1983 version was re-released on iTunes April 10, 2020.</description>
			 <year>1982</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Still Got The Blues</title>
			 <artist>Gary Moore</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/f2/Stillgottheblues.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Virgin records</company>
			 <description>Still Got the Blues is the eighth solo studio album by Northern Irish guitarist Gary Moore, released in 1990.</description>
			 <year>1990</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Eros</title>
			 <artist>Eros Ramazzotti</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/d/df/Erosselftitled.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>IT</country>
			 <company>BMG</company>
			 <description>Eros is the first greatest hits album by Italian pop/rock singer Eros Ramazzotti, released in 1997 on the BMG label.</description>
			 <year>1997</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>One Night Only</title>
			 <artist>Bee Gees</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/ee/Bee_Gees_One_Night_Only.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Polydor</company>
			 <description>One Night Only is a live album and DVD/Blu-ray by the Bee Gees.</description>
			 <year>1998</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Sylvias Mother</title>
			 <artist>Dr.Hook</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/46/Sylvia%27s_Mother_-_Dr._Hook.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>CBS</company>
			 <description>Doctor Hook, later released as Sylvia's Mother, is the debut studio album by American country rock band Dr. Hook & the Medicine Show, released in 1972.</description>
			 <year>1973</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Maggie May</title>
			 <artist>Rod Stewart</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/3d/Maggiereason.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Pickwick</company>
			 <description>"Maggie May" is a song co-written by singer Rod Stewart and Martin Quittenton, and performed by Rod Stewart on his album Every Picture Tells a Story, released in 1971.</description>
			 <year>1990</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Romanza</title>
			 <artist>Andrea Bocelli</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/b/b0/BocelliRomanzaAlbumCover.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>IT</country>
			 <company>Polydor</company>
			 <description>Romanza is the first compilation album by Italian singer Andrea Bocelli, released internationally in 1996.</description>
			 <year>1996</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>When a Man Loves a Woman</title>
			 <artist>Percy Sledge</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/6/62/When_a_Man_Loves_a_Woman_cover.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>Atlantic</company>
			 <description>"When a Man Loves a Woman" is a song written by Calvin Lewis and Andrew Wright and first recorded by Percy Sledge in 1966 at Norala Sound Studio in Sheffield, Alabama.</description>
			 <year>1987</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Black Angel</title>
			 <artist>Savage Rose</artist>
			 <artwork>https://img.discogs.com/sJR_dx-WgNftHfoSTLE2CMGfqRE=/fit-in/300x300/filters:strip_icc():format(jpeg):mode_rgb():quality(40)/discogs-images/R-1219100-1368122210-8493.jpeg.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>DK</country>
			 <company>Mega</company>
			 <description>In 1996 The Savage Rose received a Danish Music Award for the album Black Angel, which was recorded in the US. The band's debut album, The Savage Rose, was chosen as part of the Danish Culture Cyearn in 2006.</description>
			 <year>1995</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>1999 Grammy Nominees</title>
			 <artist>Many</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/9/91/Grammy41logo.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>Grammy</company>
			 <description>The Grammy Nominees is a series of various artists compilation albums celebrating the best of the music industry.</description>
			 <year>1999</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>For The Good Times</title>
			 <artist>Kenny Rogers</artist>
			 <artwork>https://img.discogs.com/rRLafBnMy3Ys4qq2xuncOw_r_3Y=/fit-in/250x252/filters:strip_icc():format(jpeg):mode_rgb():quality(90)/discogs-images/R-13629862-1557859200-1484.jpeg.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Mucik Master</company>
			 <description>The discography of Kenny Rogers, an American country music singer, consists of 39 studio albums and 80 singles, 21 of which have reached Number One on the country chart.</description>
			 <year>1995</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Big Willie Style</title>
			 <artist>Will Smith</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/b/bb/WillSmith-BigWillieStyle.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>Columbia</company>
			 <description>Big Willie Style is the debut solo album by American hip hop recording artist Will Smith.</description>
			 <year>1997</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Tupelo Honey</title>
			 <artist>Van Morrison</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/d/d9/Van_Morrison_-_Tupelo_Honey.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Polydor</company>
			 <description>Tupelo Honey is the fifth studio album by Northern Irish singer-songwriter Van Morrison.</description>
			 <year>1971</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Bridge of Spies</title>
			 <artist>T'Pau</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/1/12/TpauBridgeOfSpies.JPG</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Siren</company>
			 <description>Bridge of Spies is the debut album by British pop group T'Pau, released in September 1987.</description>
			 <year>1987</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Private Dancer</title>
			 <artist>Tina Turner</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/42/Tina_Turner_Private_Dancer_US_CD_cover_art_1984_original.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Capitol</company>
			 <description>Private Dancer is the fifth solo studio album by Tina Turner.</description>
			 <year>1983</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Midt om natten</title>
			 <artist>Kim Larsen</artist>
			 <country>DK</country>
			 <company>Medley</company>
			 <description>In the Middle of the Night (Danish: Midt om natten) is a 1984 Danish musical drama film directed by Erik Balling, which was the final film project Balling ever directed before his death.</description>
			 <year>1983</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>The Dock of the Bay</title>
			 <artist>Otis Redding</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/5/55/Dockofthebay.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>Stax Records</company>
			 <description>The Dock of the Bay is the first of a number of posthumously released Otis Redding albums, and his seventh studio album.</description>
			 <year>1968</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Picture Book</title>
			 <artist>Simply Red</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/e5/PictureBookSimplyRedalbumcover.png</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Elektra</company>
			 <description>Picture Book is the debut album by British pop and soul group Simply Red, released in October 1985.</description>
			 <year>1985</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Red</title>
			 <artist>The Communards</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/34/Communards_Red.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>London</company>
			 <description>Red is the second album from British pop duo The Communards.</description>
			 <year>1987</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>Unchain My Heart</title>
			 <artist>Joe Cocker</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/8/8e/Joe_Cocker-Unchain_My_Heart_%28album_cover%29.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>EMI</company>
			 <description>Unchain My Heart is the eleventh studio album by Joe Cocker, released in 1987.</description>
			 <year>1987</year> </CD>
	 <CD>
			 <title>The Dark Side of The Moon</title>
			 <artist>Pink Floyd</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/3b/Dark_Side_of_the_Moon.png</artwork>
			 <country>GB</country>
			 <company>Harvest</company>
			 <description>The Dark Side of the Moon is the eighth studio album by the English rock band Pink Floyd, released on 1 March 1973 by Harvest Records. Primarily developed during live performances, the band premiered an early version of the record several months before recording began. The record was conceived as an album that focused on the pressures faced by the band during their arduous lifestyle, and dealing with the apparent mental health problems suffered by former band member Syd Barrett, who departed the group in 1968. New material was recorded in two sessions in 1972 and 1973 at Abbey Road Studios in London.</description>
			 <year>1973</year> </CD>
		<CD>
			 <title>Aja</title>
			 <artist>Steely Dan</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/49/Aja_album_cover.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>Harvest</company>
			 <description>Aja (/ˈeɪʒə/, pronounced like Asia) is the sixth studio album by the American jazz rock band Steely Dan. It was released in September 1977 by ABC Records. Recording alongside nearly 40 musicians, band leaders Donald Fagen and Walter Becker pushed Steely Dan further into experimenting with different combinations of session players while pursuing longer, more sophisticated compositions for the album.</description>
			 <year>1973</year> </CD>
		<CD>
			 <title>Return to the 36 Chambers</title>
			 <artist>Ol' Dirty Bastard</artist>
			 <artwork>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/b/bf/Odb_welfare.jpg</artwork>
			 <country>US</country>
			 <company>Elektra</company>
			 <description>Return to the 36 Chambers is the solo debut album of American rapper and Wu-Tang Clan member Ol' Dirty Bastard, released March 28, 1995 on Elektra Records in the United States. It was the second solo album, after Method Man's Tical, to be released from the nine-member Wu-Tang clan, following the release of their debut album. Return to the 36 Chambers was primarily produced by RZA, with additional production from Ol' Dirty Bastard, and affiliates True Master and 4th Disciple. The album features guest appearances from Wu-Tang members GZA, RZA, Method Man, Raekwon, Ghostface Killah and Masta Killa, as well as several Wu-Tang affiliates and Brooklyn Zu.</description>
			 <year>1995</year> </CD>
</CATALOG>
